Agustin Bautista

903 9th Ave 53 Seattle, WA 98104

206.747.3198 abautist703@gmail.com www.agustinbautista.com

Profile

Excellent front-end web development skills with an eye for design. Fully competent building full stack web applications with experience using node.js and ruby on rails. Organized, detail-oriented and with international account management experience, I stay on top of deadlines and prioritize work decisively. Before web development, I founded and managed an organic vegetable farm.

Experience

Teaching Assistant, General Assembly

Seattle, WA - Jan 2016-present

Regular interaction with 15+ students, guiding instruction on various web development topics, debugging and communicating coding best practices. Provide assistance on several projects built in various languages and frameworks including node is and ruby on rails

Web Development Immersive, General Assembly

Seattle, WA - Sep 2015-Dec 2015

12-week program covers HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, node.js, express.js, PostgreSQL, Ruby on Rails, AngularJS, and other technologies

Organic Farmer, Jumanji Farm

Seattle, WA - May 2014-Dec 2015

Mixed veggie CSA farm incubator at Sno-Valley Tilth's Experience Farming Project. Emphasis placed on growing the highest quality vegetables following organic and biologically intensive farming practices

Senior Associate, Ogilvy Financial | Ogilvy Public Relations

Beijing - Aug 2009-Dec 2012

Supported communications and investor relations programs for various China-based US-listed companies. Responsibilities included account management, planning, strategy, and media outreach

Education

General Assembly; Seattle, WA - web development immersive, 2015 Hamilton College; Clinton, NY - B.A. cum laude, Chinese studies, 2008

Skills

Responsive Web Design | HTML5 | CSS3 | Sass | JavaScript | jQuery | Express.js | Node.js | Ruby on Rails | Bootstrap | PostgreSQL | MongoDB | Git | AngularJS | React | ES2015

References

Brian Hague, General Assembly Web Developer, Instructor — <u>brian.hague@ga.co</u>
Josh Sera, General Assembly Mobile Developer, Instructor —<u>josh.sera@ga.co</u>

Annie Ly, General Assembly Education Programs Manager — annie.ly@generalassemb.ly